{
    "id": "dd5dc2c64d6d47a9af4383208766aee4",
    "title": "Adjective or adverb: grammar exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "6d8cf2cca25e4d3694aef9a6f0aa0610",
            "title": "Adjective Or Adverb",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "If you work too …………………………………., you will fall ill.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "hard",
                        "hardly"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The country received …………………………………… any rainfall this year.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "hard",
                        "hardly"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "In a democratic country, everybody has the right to speak …………………………….",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "free",
                        "freely"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He hit the nail ................................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "hard",
                        "hardly"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The show was ……………………………………… amusing.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "high",
                        "highly"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Throw it as ………………………………………. as you can.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "high",
                        "highly"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He has ……………………………………. arrived.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "just",
                        "justly"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "All criminals must be ……………………………………….. punished for their crimes.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "just",
                        "justly"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is never ………………………………………… for work.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "late",
                        "lately"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I haven’t been to the theatre much …………………………………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "late",
                        "lately"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}